Guide to the Gerald H. Anderson Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
Gerald H. Anderson Papers
1947-2015
RG 166
Yale University Divinity School Library
40.5
(52 boxes)
These papers document the work of Gerald H. Anderson, who was a missionary educator, college president, and Director of the Overseas Ministries Study Center from 1974 to 2000. Anderson's extensive writings, lectures, and conference activities provide a valuable overview of the ecumenical mission scene during the second half of the twentieth century. A substantial portion of the collection relates to Anderson's work as editor of the Biographical Dictionary of Christian Missions. These records include drafts and materials not included in the final publication as well as correspondence with the contributors. Other areas of research interest for Anderson included Christianity in the Philippines, Jewish-Christian relations, and the history of the International Association for Mission Studies.
Anderson, Gerald H.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Gerald H. Anderson, 2001-2016
Conditions Governing Access
Open to qualified researchers.
Biographical / Historical
Gerald H. Anderson was born in 1930. He was a Methodist missionary in the Philippines from 1960 to 1970, serving as professor of church history and ecumenics as well as the academic dean of Union Theological Seminary in Manila. Upon returning to the United States, he was elected president of Scarritt College in Nashville and was also professor of world Christianity there. From 1973 to 1974, Anderson was a senior research associate in the Southeast Asia Program at Cornell University. In 1974 he was appointed as Associate Director of the Overseas Ministries Study Center and in 1976 became Executive Director of OMSC and editor of the International Bulletin of Missionary Research. Anderson was a founder and president of the American Society of Missiology and a participant in many ecumenical groups such as the International Missionary Council, World Council of Churches Commission on World Mission and Evangelism, Lausanne Committee Task Force on Jewish Evangelism, and the Kennedy Institute Jewish-Christian-Muslim Trialogue. Among his many published works, Anderson was co-editor with Stephen Neill and John Goodwin of the Concise Dictionary of the Christian World Mission, co-editor and author (with Thomas Stransky) of the series Mission Trends, co-editor of Mission Legacies, editor of Biographical Dictionary of Christian Missions, and author of Witness to World Christianity: the International Association for Mission Studies, 1972-2012. For more detailed biographical information, see Series IV, Personal Items and Memorabilia, Biographical Documentation.
Scope and Contents
This collection primarily documents Gerald H. Anderson's work as missionary educator in the Philippines, author, editor, and participant in many ecumenical mission conferences and groups. While Anderson was Associate Director and then Executive Director of the Overseas Ministries Study Center from 1974-2000, this collection does not document his work with OMSC except through some Director's reports. The collection was substantially augmented and re-ordered in 2013 as records from throughout Anderson's career were added to the existing collection that primarily documented his work on the Biographical Dictionary of Christian Missions, a work which includes extensive and comprehensive coverage of Christian missions with 2,400 original signed biographies by 350 authors from 45 countries.
Arrangement
I. Correspondence
II. Writings, Lectures, Research Files
III. Conference and Consultation Activities
IV. Personal Items and Memorabilia
V. Audio-Visual Material
Missionaries -- Biography -- Dictionaries; Ecumenical movement; Anderson, Gerald H.
- Correspondence, 1959-2015; Series I
  - Family correspondence
    - From wife Joanne Pemberton Anderson and daughter Allison, 1966-1980, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Circular letters
    - From Joanne and Jerry Anderson in the Philippines, 1960-1964 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Family newsletters, 1961-2015 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - General correspondence
    Scope and Contents
    See additional correspondence regarding writings of Anderson in the "Writings and Research" subseries.
    - Gowing, Peter, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      Gowing was a professor of Christian History and Doctrine at Silliman University, Dumaguete City, Philippines
    - Gowing, Peter, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Gowing, Peter, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Gowing, Peter, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Gowing, Peter, 1967-1976 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Gowing, Peter, 1978-1983 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - International Association for Mission Studies, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 9)
      See also: Writings and Research: IAMS History
    - International Leadership Group - Christian Study Center in Peking University, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Methodist Church, Division of World Missions, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 11)
      Regarding service at Union Theological Seminary, Manila, Philippines
    - Neill, Stephen C. (Bishop), including regarding the Concise Dictionary of the Christian World Nission. Edited by Stephen Neill, Gerald H. Anderson and] John Goodwin, 1963-1966 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Neill, Stephen C. (Bishop), including regarding the Concise Dictionary of the Christian World Nission, 1967-1984 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Regarding German edition of Concise Dictionary of the Christian World Mission, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Regarding "Sermons to Men of Other Faiths and Traditions" - correspondence with Abingdon Press, 1964-1966 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Regarding "Sermons to Men of Other Faiths and Traditions" - correspondence with potential contributors, including from Martin Luther King, Jr., Henry P. Van Dusen, 1964-1964 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Regarding "Sermons to Men of Other Faiths and Traditions" - correspondence with contributors A - H, including from Robert McAfee Brown, Carl Henry, 1964-1965 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Regarding "Sermons to Men of Other Faiths and Traditions" - correspondence with contributors L - M, including from Eric Lincoln, Martin Marty, 1964-1965 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Regarding "Sermons to Men of Other Faiths and Traditions" - correspondence with contributors N - W, including from D. T. Niles, John Wright, 1964-1965 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Regarding "Towards the 21st Century in Christian Mission", Festschrift for Anderson, 1992-1995 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Stowe, David; Union Theological Seminary (Manila); Union Theological Seminary (New York); Yale Divinity School Library, 1959-1986 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Tributes
    - Letters of tribute presented at time of retirement, 2000 Jun 9 (Box 29, Folder 2989)
    - Letters of tribute from mission executives' study group, 1995-2000 (Box 29, Folder 2988)
- Writings, Lectures, Research Files, 1957-2012; Series II
  This series includes correspondence regarding works published by Anderson as well as texts.
  - Bibliography of Anderson's published works, 2012 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Bibliographical projects
    - Christianity in Southeast Asia, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Christianity in Japan, Korea, and Oceania: A Bibliographical Guide, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - 700 Basic Books for Studies in the Christian World Mission: A Bibliographical Guide, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Articles / chapters
    - Including "The Challenge of the Ecumenical Movement to Methodism", "The Theology of Missions: 1928-1958" (Abstract of Anderson's dissertation for Boston University Graduate School), 1960 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Including "A Theocentric Approach to Christian Mission", "Christian Missions and the Meaning of History", "The Christian Mission Reconsidered", 1961-1963 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Including "Four Centuries of Christianity in the Philippines: An Interpretation", "John Wesley, A Biographical Sermon", "Missionary Readings on the Philippines", "A Select Bibliography on the Theology of the Christian Mission", 1964-1965 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Including "Kraemer and After: A Survey Review Article", "The Protestant Churches in the Philippines Since Independence", 1966-1967 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Including "The Church and the Jewish People: Some Theological Issues and Missiological Concerns", "The Philippines: Reluctant Beneficiary of the Missionary Impulse in Europe", 1968-1976 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Articles relating to Commission to Study the Mission of the United Methodist Church, 1984-1988 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Including "American Protestants in Pursuit of MIssion: 1886-1986", "Theology of Religions and Missiology: A Time of Testing", 1988, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Including "Missionary Biography: A Select Annotated Bibliography" and American National Biography articles on Harlan Page Beach and Robert Allen Hume, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Including "Christian Mission in A.D. 2000: A Glance Backward", "The Role of the Bibliographia Missionaria in Contemporary Missiology" (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Contributions to Festschrift for Fr. Sebastian Karotemprel, 2000-2001 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Including "Peter Parker and the Introduction of Western Medicine in China", "Fighting Missionary Malaise", "The Legacy of Peter Parker, M.D., 2006-2013 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Regarding booklength works
    - Theology of the Christian Mission (1961)
      - Publicity leaflet, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Sermons for Men of Other Faiths and Traditions (1966)
      - Reviews, publicity, agreement, 1964-1966 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Witnessing to the Kingdom Melbourne and Beyond (1982)
      - Correspondence, content (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Biographical Dictionary of Christian Mission
      - Authors File
        - Index to Authors (Box 1, Folder 1)
        - Author Address List (Box 1, Folder 2)
        - Adeney, Miriam, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
        - Ahrens, Theodor, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
        - Anastasios, Yannoulatos, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
        - Anderson, Gerald H. (Box 1, Folder 6)
        - Angleviel Frederic, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 7)
        - Amaladoss, Michael, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
        - Arevalo, C. G., 1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
        - Arcilla, Jose S., 1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
        - Augustijn, C., 1993 (Box 1, Folder 11)
        - Askew, Thomas A., 1993 (Box 1, Folder 12)
        - Athyal, Abraham, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
        - Athyal, Abraham, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 14)
        - Austin, Alvyn, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 15)
        - Blackie, Nansie, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 16)
        - Balia, D. M., 1996 (Box 1, Folder 17)
        - Bakker, D., 1994 (Box 1, Folder 18)
        - Barrett, David B., 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 19)
        - Baumann, Arnulf H., 1993 (Box 1, Folder 20)
        - Bays, Daniel H., 1993 (Box 1, Folder 21)
        - Bebbington, David, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 22)
        - Becken, Hans-Jurgen, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 23)
        - Bediako, Kwame, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 24)
        - Beeby, H. Daniel, 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 25)
        - Beffa, Pierre, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 26)
        - Bellagamba, Anthony, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 27)
        - Benedeto, Robert, 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 28)
        - Bennett, Clinton, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 29)
        - Bernard, Edith, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 30)
        - Bennett, John C., 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 31)
        - Bevans, Stephen, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 32)
        - Bijlefeld, W.A., 1993 (Box 1, Folder 33)
        - Binfield, Clyde, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 34)
        - Bireley, Robert, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 35)
        - Bingle, Richard, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 36)
        - Bischofberger, Otto, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 37)
        - Blackie, Nansie, 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 38)
        - Bloch-Hoell, Nils, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 39)
        - Blumhofer, Edith, 1993-1997 (Box 1, Folder 40)
        - Boer, Harry, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 41)
        - Bohr, P. Richard, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 42)
        - Bonk, Jonathon, 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 43)
        - Bollinger, Edward E., 1993 (Box 1, Folder 44)
        - Bowden, Henry W., 1993 (Box 1, Folder 45)
        - Brackney, William H., 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 46)
        - Brown, G. Thompson, 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 47)
        - Brunner, Paul, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 48)
        - Brummel, Mark J., 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 49)
        - Bundy, David, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 50)
        - Burkle, Horst, 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 51)
        - Burridge, Kenelm, 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 52)
        - Camps, Arnulf, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 53)
        - Caraman, Philip, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 54)
        - Carman, John, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 55)
        - Carpenter, Joel, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 56)
        - Carson, Penny, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 57)
        - Castro, Emilio, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 58)
        - Chandran, Russell, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 59)
        - Chandrakanthan, A.J.V. (Box 1, Folder 60)
        - Chatfield, Joan, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 61)
        - Choo, Cindy Swanson, 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 62)
        - Clasper, Paul, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 63)
        - Cleary, Edward L., 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 64)
        - Clements, Keith, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 65)
        - Cliff, Norman H., 1995 (Box 1, Folder 66)
        - Clifford, Paul R., 1993 (Box 1, Folder 67)
        - Clouse, Robert G., 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 68)
        - Cobb, Alice, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 69)
        - Cohen, Thomas, 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 70)
        - Coleman, Mary Frances, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 71)
        - Conn, Harvie M., 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 72)
        - Constantelos, Demetrios, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 73)
        - Coote, Robert, 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 74)
        - Corwin, Gary, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 75)
        - Couchelll, Dimitrios, 1993-1997 (Box 1, Folder 76)
        - Covell, Ralph R., 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 77)
        - Cox, James, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 78)
        - Cracknell, Kenneth, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 79)
        - Craig, Terrence L., 1995 (Box 1, Folder 80)
        - Cragg, Kenneth, 1992-1995 (Box 1, Folder 81)
        - Craig, Terrence L., 1995 (Box 1, Folder 82)
        - Clyde, Crews, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 83)
        - Crummey, Donald, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 84)
        - Cummins, J.S., 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 85)
        - Curran, Emmet, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 86)
        - Daneel, Inus, 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 87)
        - Daneel, Inus, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 88)
        - Darr, Dick L., 1993 (Box 1, Folder 89)
        - Darr, Richard, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 90)
        - Dauenhauer, Richard, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 91)
        - David, Mohan D., 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 92)
        - Davidson, Allan, 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 93)
        - Davies, Ron, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 94)
        - de Gruchy, John W., 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 95)
        - de Jong, Chr. G.F., 1993-1997 (Box 1, Folder 96)
        - Deiros, Pablo A., 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 97)
        - Dekar, Paul R., 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 98)
        - Detzler, Wayne A., 1993 (Box 1, Folder 99)
        - Deyneka, Peter, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 100)
        - Dhamaraj, Jason S., 1994 (Box 1, Folder 101)
        - DiNoia, Joseph, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 102)
        - Donders, J.G., 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 103)
        - Douglas, Ian, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 104)
        - Downs, Fred, 1993-1997 (Box 1, Folder 105)
        - Dreydoppel, Otto, 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 106)
        - Dries, Angelyn, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 107)
        - Drummond, Richard H., 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 108)
        - Dulles, Avery, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 109)
        - Dupuis, Jacques, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 110)
        - Duffy, Joan, 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 111)
        - Durnbaugh, Don, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 112)
        - Dussel, Enrique, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 113)
        - Dyck, Cornelius J., 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 114)
        - Ellingworth, Paul, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 115)
        - Ellis, Jane, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 116)
        - Eltscher, Sue, 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 117)
        - Emilsen, William W., 1994 (Box 1, Folder 118)
        - End Th. van den, 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 119)
        - Engelsviken, Tormod, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 120)
        - Enklaar, I.H., 1993-1997 (Box 1, Folder 121)
        - Erickson, John, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 122)
        - Escobar, Samuel, 1993-1997 (Box 1, Folder 123)
        - Esteban, Rafael, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 124)
        - Etherington, Norman, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 125)
        - Fisher, James, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 126)
        - Fitts, Leroy, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 127)
        - Fogarty, Gerald, 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 128)
        - Forman, Charles W., 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 129)
        - Forrester, Duncan, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 130)
        - Fox, M.J., 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 131)
        - Frank, Albert, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 132)
        - Fukada, Robert M., 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 133)
        - Foley, Edward, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 134)
        - Fox, Joy, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 135)
        - Franzen, Ruth, 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 136)
        - Fraser, Angus, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 137)
        - Frykenberg, Robert Eric, 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 138)
        - Fugmann, Gernot, 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 139)
        - Garrett, Paul D., 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 140)
        - Garrett, John, 1993-1997 (Box 1, Folder 141)
        - Gensichen, D.H.W., 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 142)
        - Gladstone, J.W., 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 143)
        - Gittins, Anthony J., 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 144)
        - Glasser, Arthur, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 145)
        - Gordon, Karen L., 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 146)
        - Goodpasture, H. McKennie, 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 147)
        - Goodwin, John, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 148)
        - Gordon, Karen, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 149)
        - Gorski, Jan, 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 150)
        - Gort, Jerald, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 151)
        - Gration, John, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 152)
        - Gray, Richard, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 153)
        - Grayson, James, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 154)
        - Griffiths, Leslie, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 155)
        - Grundmann, Christopher H., 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 156)
        - Gutierrez, Lucio, 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 157)
        - Haas, Waltraud, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 158)
        - Hackett, Rosalind I.J., 1993 (Box 2, Folder 159)
        - Hair, P.E.H., 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 160)
        - Haile, Getatchew, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 161)
        - Halliburton, Gordon, 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 162)
        - Hallencreutz, Carl F., 1993 (Box 2, Folder 163)
        - Hamilton, Michael S., 1994 (Box 2, Folder 164)
        - Harakas, Stanley S., 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 165)
        - Hanciles, Jehu J., 1994 (Box 2, Folder 166)
        - Harley, C. David, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 167)
        - Harris, John, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 168)
        - Hastings, Adrian, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 169)
        - Heideman, Eugene, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 170)
        - Harper, Susan Billington, 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 171)
        - Hassing, Per, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 172)
        - Hedlund, Roger E., 1994-1996 (Box 2, Folder 173)
        - Hendrick, John R., 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 174)
        - Hendricks, Barbara, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 175)
        - Henkel, Willi, 1992-1997 (Box 2, Folder 176)
        - Henxham, Irving, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 177)
        - Hesselgrave, David J., n.d. (Box 2, Folder 178)
        - Hexham, Irving, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 179)
        - Hezel, Francis X., 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 180)
        - Higgins, Susan, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 181)
        - Hillman, Eugene, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 182)
        - Hodgson, Janet, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 183)
        - Hitchen, John, 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 184)
        - Hoedemaker, Libertus A., 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 185)
        - Hoekema, A.G., 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 186)
        - Hogan, Edmund, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 187)
        - Hogendorp, Marjo A., 1994-1996 (Box 2, Folder 188)
        - Hogg, W. Richey, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 189)
        - Holger, Brent Hansen, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 190)
        - Hofmeyr, J.W., 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 191)
        - Hood, George A., 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 192)
        - Hooker, Roger, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 193)
        - Hopko, Thomas, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 194)
        - Horner, Norman A., 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 195)
        - Hosie, John, 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 196)
        - Howard, David M., 1993 (Box 2, Folder 197)
        - Hunt, Everett N., 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 198)
        - Hoyle, Lydia Huffman, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 199)
        - Hunt, Keith, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 200)
        - Hunt, Robert A., 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 201)
        - Hunter, George G., 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 202)
        - Hutchison, William R., 1993 (Box 2, Folder 203)
        - Ion, A. Hamish, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 204)
        - Jacobs, Sylvia, 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 205)
        - Jackson, Eleanor M., 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 206)
        - Jenkins, Paul, 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 207)
        - Jeroense, P.J.G., 1993-1997 (Box 2, Folder 208)
        - Johnson, R. Park, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 209)
        - Johnston, Geoffrey, 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 210)
        - Jones, John N., 1994 (Box 2, Folder 211)
        - Jongeneel, J.A.B., 1993-1997 (Box 2, Folder 212)
        - Jones, Richard J., 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 213)
        - Jong, G.F.de, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 214)
        - Joose, J.L., 1994 (Box 2, Folder 215)
        - Kalu, Ogbu U., 1993-1997 (Box 2, Folder 216)
        - Kang, Wi Jo, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 217)
        - Karotemprel S., n.d. (Box 2, Folder 218)
        - Kasdorf, Hans, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 219)
        - Kauffman, Christopher, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 220)
        - Kerr, David A., 1993-1997 (Box 2, Folder 221)
        - Kidd, Karen, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 222)
        - King, Gail, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 223)
        - Kings, Graham, 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 224)
        - Kipp, Rita Smith, 1994-1996 (Box 2, Folder 225)
        - Kirk, Andrew, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 226)
        - Klaiber, Jeffrey, 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 227)
        - Kirika, Gerishon M., 1994 (Box 2, Folder 228)
        - Kjaer-Hansen, Kai, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 229)
        - Kool, Anne-Marie, 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 230)
        - Klootwijk, Eeuwout, 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 231)
        - Kollbrunner, Fritz, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 232)
        - Kpobi, David, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 233)
        - Kroeger, James H., 1993 (Box 2, Folder 234)
        - Krummel, John W., 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 235)
        - Kvarme Ole Chr. M., 1993 (Box 2, Folder 236)
        - Kwok, Pui-Lan, 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 237)
        - Lacy, Creighton, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 238)
        - Lagerwerf, Leny, 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 239)
        - Lahiff, Bartholomew, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 240)
        - Langer, Erick D., 1994 (Box 2, Folder 241)
        - Lamb, Christopher, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 242)
        - Lan, Kwok Pui, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 243)
        - Levesque, Joseph, 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 244)
        - Lineham, Peter, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 245)
        - Li, Li, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 246)
        - Liefeld, Walter, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 247)
        - Littell, Franklin H., 1995 (Box 2, Folder 248)
        - Lodwick, Kathleen, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 249)
        - Loftus, Margaret, 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 250)
        - Long, Charles H., 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 251)
        - Lutzbetak, Louis J., 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 252)
        - Lopez-Gay, Jesus, 1993-1998 (Box 2, Folder 253)
        - Lott, Eric, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 254)
        - Ludwig, Frieder, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 255)
        - Lynch, Cyprian, 1993-1997 (Box 2, Folder 256)
        - MacInnis, Donald, 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 257)
        - Mackey, James, 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 258)
        - Maclin, H.T., 1993 (Box 2, Folder 259)